&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在它开始谈论作用域实际上可以是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now it start to talk about the idea that scopes can actually be
嵌套在彼此的内部。
nested inside of each other.
所以我们还要进一步延伸这个桶的比喻。
So we're gonna even further stretch that bucket metaphor.
现在我们讨论的是桶的侧面，桶的侧面
Now we're talking about the bucket within the side of a bucket within the side of
水桶，真的很奇怪。
the bucket, it gets really weird.
但我们会一直有水桶的，好吗？
But we're gonna have buckets all the way down, okay?
[笑]
[LAUGH].
所以让我们用和以前完全相同的方式来快速处理这件事，
So let's process this quickly exactly the same way as we have before,
完全一样的规则，好吗？
same rules entirely, okay?
我们从一号线开始，这是一种什么样的大理石？
We start by looking at line one, that's a what kind of marble?
第一行是正式声明，使？
Line one is a formal declaration that makes a?
&gt；&gt；类：红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Class: Red marble.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：制作红色大理石，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Makes a red marble, right?
我们要创造一个红色的大理石。
We're gonna create a red marble.
第三行是一个正式的声明，创建了一个什么颜色的大理石？
Line three is a formal declaration that creates a what color marble?
&gt；&gt；类：红色。
&gt;&gt; Class: Red.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第四行是一个创建What的声明
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line four is a declaration that creates a what
彩色大理石？
color marble?
&gt；&gt；类：蓝色。
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：蓝色大理石，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A blue marble, right?
现在我们在蓝色范围内。
Now we're inside of the blue scope.
第六行是创建什么颜色模块的声明？
Line six is a declaration that creates what color module?
&gt；&gt；类：蓝色。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：蓝色模块，
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The blue module,
因为Ask在另一个类的范围内，对吗？
cuz ask is in the scope of the other class, right?
函数声明使其标识符位于其封闭范围内，
Function declarations make their identifier in their enclosing scope,
这很关键，记住这一点。
that's critical, keep that in mind.
好的，那么我们在Ask内部，它是由什么颜色范围组成的？
All right, so then we're inside of ask and it's made of what color scope?
&gt；&gt；学生：黄色。&gt；&gt；类：[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Student: Yellow. &gt;&gt; Class: [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：当然，在我们身上改变一下。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sure, change it up on us.
我们一直在用绿色，但我们还是换成黄色吧。
We've been using green, but let's switch to yellow.
没有混淆。
No confusion.
[笑]好的
[LAUGH] Okay,
我要坚持绿色，因为如果我不说绿色的话，我就会说错的话。
I'm gonna stick with green cuz I'm gonna say something wrong if I don't say green.
我们已经创建了一个绿色范围。
We've created a green scope.
没有要创建的弹珠，但有对大理石的引用。
There's no marbles to create, but there are references to marbles.
所以在第七行，当我们推荐老师时，
So on line seven when we reference teacher,
那会是什么样的大理石呢？
what kind of marble is that gonna be?
7号线的老师是什么颜色的大理石？
What color marble is the teacher on line 7?
&gt；&gt；类：蓝色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Class: Blue marble.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：蓝色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Blue marble.
第七行的问题是什么颜色的大理石？
And what color marble is the question from line 7?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那是一个绿色的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's a green one.
&gt；&gt；类：它是蓝色的，因为问题来自于函数ask。
&gt;&gt; Class: It's blue because question comes with function ask.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：问题是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So question is a variable inside of
函数的范围问，对吗？
the scope of the function ask, right?
那会是什么颜色的大理石呢？
So what color marble would that have been?
&gt；&gt；类：绿色。
&gt;&gt; Class: Green.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：应该是绿色的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Would've been green.
即使它没有var，
Even though it doesn't have a var there,
参数在该作用域中正式创建标识符。
a parameter is formally creating an identifier in that scope.
所以我们有一个老师是一个蓝色的大理石，问题是一个绿色的大理石。
So we'd have a teacher being a blue marble and question being a green marble.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我们有了一个范围，这就在范围内，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now we have a scope and that's within the scope, and
那是在一个范围内。
that's within a scope.
顺便说一下，这个范围解决方案，当我们问一个问题的时候，基本上就是在做
And that scope resolution by the way, when we ask for a question is basically doing
在处理过程中，它说，嘿，老师，您是否存在于Ask范围内？
that processing where it says, hey, teacher, do you exist in the ask scope?
然后，当它没有，然后我们到外面的范围和
And then, when it doesn't then we go out to the outer scope and
我们碰巧在那里找到了它。
we happened to find it there.
但如果我们不这样做，我们就会继续下去，所以
But if we didn't, we would have go on and keep going, so
如果你真的想疯狂的话，你可以深入50层，好吗？
you could go 50 levels deep if you really wanna go crazy with it, okay?
那么问题的价值是什么呢？
So what is the value of question?
&gt；&gt；类：为什么？
&gt;&gt; Class: Why?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它是字符串，为什么？，因为在第10行，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is the string, Why?, because on line 10,
当我们执行第10行时。
when we execute line 10.
我们在那里有一个我们可能不得不查找的值，但是
We have a value there which we might have had to look up, but
在这种情况下，它是一个字面意思。
in this case it's a literal.
那么弦线会发生什么变化呢？
And what happens to the string line?
&gt；&gt；类：它被传递-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它被分配给
&gt;&gt; Class: It gets passed- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It gets assigned to
变量问题，所以
the variable question, so
该执行发生在Ask开始执行之前的第10行。
that execution happens at line 10 before ask starts executing.
所以当我们要求得到我们找到的大理石时，这是一个绿色的大理石
So when we then ask for the marble that we find, which is a green marble and
我们问题的价值，是吗？
we ask for the value of question, it is?
&gt；&gt；类：为什么？
&gt;&gt; Class: Why?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是引言，为什么？，这是字符串，为什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's the quote, Why?, it's the string, Why?.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第14行会发生什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's gonna happen with line 14?
第14行是如何执行的？
How does line 14 execute?
&gt；&gt；类：它将显示为红色按钮。
&gt;&gt; Class: It's gonna look red button.
&gt；&gt；学生：未定义？
&gt;&gt; Student: It's undefined?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们需要做和以前一样的叙事，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We need to do the same narrative as before,
不要草率下结论。
don't jump to conclusions.
叙事是如何工作的？
How does the narrative work?
&gt；&gt；类：全局范围。
&gt;&gt; Class: Global scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，全球范围内，我有一个，什么样的参考？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey global scope, I have a, what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；类：一个源。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：源参考
&gt;&gt; Class: A source. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A source reference for
识别码问，听说过吗？答案是？
an Identifier code ask, ever heard of it and the answer is?
&gt；&gt；类别：第&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么错误是什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Class: No. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what's the error?
&gt；&gt；类：参考询问。
&gt;&gt; Class: The reference ask.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：参考询问，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The reference ask, okay?
即使Ask存在于程序中，
Even though ask exist within the program,
它不存在于我们目前有权访问的任何范围内。
it doesn't exist in any scope that we have access to at this moment.
因此它是一个未声明的变量，不像autoglobals，
So it is therefore an undeclared variable unlike the autoglobals,
因为我们没有严格的模式。
because we're not in strict mode.
与自动球体不同，自动球体会为您创建一个大理石。
Unlike autoglobals which go ahead and create a marble for you.
如果源引用了未声明的变量，
If you have a source referenced to a variable that is undeclared,
它总是抛出ReferenceError，好吗？
it always throws a ReferenceError, okay?
这就是为什么理解目标引用和
That's why it's critical to understand the difference between a target reference and
源引用。
a source reference.
至少如果你处于非严格模式。
At least if you're in non-strict mode.
一旦进入严格模式，它们的行为完全相同，所以
Once you go to strict mode, they both behave exactly the same, so
它停止了目标与参考的关系。
it stops mattering as much target versus reference.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我们将在这里看到一个引用，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we're gonna see a reference here,
ReferenceError在这里的第14行。
ReferenceError here on line 14.
怎么了？
Yes?
&gt；&gt；学生：当我们传递字符串时，为什么要问
&gt;&gt; Student: When we're passing the string why to ask
在第十行-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。
on line ten- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；学生：幕后有没有，
&gt;&gt; Student: Is there behind the scenes,
JavaScript是不是在某种程度上说远问题等于为什么？
is JavaScript saying far question equals why at some point?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：有点，是的，有点。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sort of, yeah, sort of.
&gt；&gt；学生：好的。
&gt;&gt; Student: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我认为从概念上讲，思考论点是可行的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think conceptually it works to think about arguments
被分配给参数。
being assigned to parameters.
技术上不是这样的，但它已经足够接近了，它适用于
It's not technically that, but it's close enough that it works for
这个特殊的叙事练习。
this particular narrative exercise.